(this["webpackJsonpagile-pm-questions"]=this["webpackJsonpagile-pm-questions"]||[]).push([[0],{36:function(e,t,o){e.exports=o(46)},41:function(e,t,o){},46:function(e,t,o){"use strict";o.r(t);var r=o(0),i=o.n(r),n=o(7),a=o.n(n),s=(o(41),o(26)),c=o(27),l=o(18),h=o(31),u=o(30),d=o(4),m=o(80),p=o(87),x=o(84),f=o(85),g=o(86),b=o(28),w=[{question:" Stakeholders must be prepared to accept that, as they understand more about the solution being developed ?",answers:[{text:"Change is inevitable",correct:!0},{text:"Change will always be a problem",correct:!1},{text:"Change must be restricted",correct:!1},{text:"Change will cause delays to the timescale",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which AgilePM principle is specifically supported by the concept of 'Build a one-team culture'?",answers:[{text:"Collaborate",correct:!0},{text:"Deliver on time",correct:!1},{text:"Never compromise quality",correct:!1},{text:"Build incrementally from firm foundations",correct:!1}]},{question:"The Agile Project Manager... :",answers:[{text:"..is expected to leave the detailed planning of the actual delivery of the product(s) to the Team Leader and members",correct:!0},{text:"..plans the detail of the actual delivery of the product(s), but validates the outcome with a Facilitated Workshop, in line with the AgilePM concept of empowerment",correct:!1},{text:"..is empowered to replace the Timebox Plans with better ones that s/he has created",correct:!1},{text:".. has to delegate responsibility to the Solution Development Team, but still needs to be the final decision maker for all day-to-day decisions, to ensure the right solution is actually created.",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which of these statements is true?",answers:[{text:"AgilePM can be used to complement other project management disciplines such as PRINCE2 and PMI without duplication of effort",correct:!0},{text:"AgilePM removes the need for using any other project management discipline such a PRINCE2\u2122 or PMI",correct:!1},{text:"Project managers need to decide whether to use PRINCE2\u2122 (or PMI) or to go agile",correct:!1},{text:"Choosing an AgilePM approach means that management becomes unnecessary",correct:!1}]},{question:"AgilePM recognises four parameters, these are",answers:[{text:"Time, cost, features and quality",correct:!0},{text:"Time, cost, mandatory features, optional features",correct:!1},{text:"Must Haves, Should Haves, Could Haves, Won't Haves",correct:!1},{text:"Requirements, Time, Cost, Contingency",correct:!1}]},{question:"What does AgilePM state about the stakeholders attitude?",answers:[{text:"Stakeholders must be prepared to accept that change is inevitable as they understand more about the solution being developed",correct:!0},{text:"Stakeholders must be prepared to avoid change where possible in order to deliver on time",correct:!1},{text:"Stakeholders must be prepared to approve all changes, regardless of size or impact",correct:!1},{text:"Stakeholders must delegate all decision making down to the empowered team members",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which of these is a specific risk to an AgilePM project?",answers:[{text:"Swapping resources in and out of the team",correct:!0},{text:"Not having all the detail agreed at the start",correct:!1},{text:"The Business change their minds",correct:!1},{text:"Unwillingness to commit to final sign-off",correct:!1}]},{question:"What are the basic building blocks of the AgilePM approach?",answers:[{text:"Philosophy, Principles, Process, People, Products, Practices",correct:!0},{text:"Attitude, behaviour, team, deliverables, lifecycle",correct:!1},{text:"Deliver on time, communicate",correct:!1},{text:"Everything is negotiable, change is a fact of life",correct:!1}]},{question:"Delivering products on time ..",answers:[{text:"..is a desirable outcome for a project",correct:!0},{text:".. is something the business ask for but is unlikely to be achieved",correct:!1},{text:"..is not possible because the business keep changing their minds",correct:!1},{text:"..is far less important than delivering the whole solution",correct:!1}]},{question:"Collaboration ...",answers:[{text:"encourages increased understanding and greater speed",correct:!0},{text:"results in a lack of discipline within the team",correct:!1},{text:".. encourages the business to take over the project",correct:!1},{text:"..allows the team to deliver twice as much in half the time",correct:!1}]},{question:"In AgilePM",answers:[{text:"a solution has to be 'good enough', no more, no less",correct:!0},{text:"..quality will be reduced in order to meet the deadlines",correct:!1},{text:"..quality is negotiable right until the first Deployment",correct:!1},{text:"The highest level of quality is our goal",correct:!1}]},{question:"What does an Outline Plan contain?",answers:[{text:"A detailed plan for the work of the Foundations phase",correct:!0},{text:"A definition of the products in each Timebox",correct:!1},{text:"A full schedule of timeboxes and their agreed content, plus any other activities for the delivery of project products",correct:!1},{text:"A high level overview of the project, assessing its feasibility",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which of these statements is true.",answers:[{text:"Where a project is time-driven, choosing a traditional waterfall approach is very risky, because delivering 100% is the driving force rather than time being the driving force",correct:!0},{text:"Choosing a traditional (waterfall) approach is very risky, because this approach does not work",correct:!1},{text:"Choosing a traditional (waterfall) approach is very risky, because this approach does not work",correct:!1},{text:"The Project manager should have the final decision on the approach to be taken, since the Project manager owns the Risk Log",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which of these statements is true for AgilePM projects?",answers:[{text:"The level of business commitment for this project should be quantified and discussed in the early stages.",correct:!0},{text:"The level of business commitment on the project is negotiable, and must be increased if the project hits problems",correct:!1},{text:"Business commitment is requested on an ad-hoc basis, whenever the Solution Developers need advice and guidance",correct:!1},{text:"AgilePM projects only work if the business commit someone full-time to the Solution Development Team",correct:!1}]},{question:"What does AgilePM provide to help assess potential risk areas to be addressed?",answers:[{text:"Project Approach Questionnaire",correct:!0},{text:"Agile / Traditional Decision Table",correct:!1},{text:"Risk Assessment Questionnaire",correct:!1},{text:"AgilePM Applicability Questionnaire",correct:!1}]},{question:"In an AgilePM project...",answers:[{text:"requirements at Development Timebox level are stated in terms of Objectives",correct:!0},{text:"...requirement detail should be signed off by the end of Foundations",correct:!1},{text:"...requirement detail should not be documented; this is how infinite flexibility is achieved",correct:!1},{text:"requirements evolve; as the project progresses they become more detailed",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which of these statements is true?",answers:[{text:"AgilePM ensures successful agile product delivery, but needs the formality of a project management method to ensure agile does not get out of control",correct:!0},{text:"To be successful, AgilePM needs a waterfall project management lifecycle used alongside it",correct:!1},{text:"AgilePM has one framework for project management and a second framework for product delivery",correct:!1},{text:"AgilePM integrates a project management lifecycle and a product development lifecycle into a single framework",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which of these contain only AgilePM roles?",answers:[{text:"Business Ambassador, Business Sponsor, Technical Co-ordinator",correct:!0},{text:"Senior Supplier, Executive Sponsor, Business Visionary",correct:!1},{text:"Business Advisor, Business User, Business Visionary",correct:!1},{text:"Product Owner, Scrum Master, Team Members",correct:!1}]},{question:"Provided the team can demonstrate control over what they are doing, it is important that ....",answers:[{text:"the practice of \u2018management by exception\u2019 is employed by the Project Manager",correct:!0},{text:"the practice of 'management by control' is employed by the Project Manager",correct:!1},{text:"the practice of 'management by absence' is employed by the Project Manager",correct:!1},{text:"the practice of 'management by apathy' is employed by the Project Manager",correct:!1}]},{question:"As part of AgilePM\u2019s drive for clear and continuous communication, modelling",answers:[{text:"can offer significant benefits in making ideas, situations and options visible",correct:!0},{text:"can offer a way of avoiding formal communication",correct:!1},{text:"emphasises the need for applying formal modelling techniques",correct:!1},{text:"replaces the need for face to face communication",correct:!1}]},{question:"In AgilePM the quality of a solution is judged\u2026",answers:[{text:".on whether it contains at least the Minimum Usable Subset and whether all delivered requirements meet the agreed standard",correct:!0},{text:"on whether 100% of the requirements have been delivered",correct:!1},{text:"on whether all the Musts, Shoulds and Coulds have been delivered",correct:!1},{text:"on whether the customer signs off every requirement that has been delivered",correct:!1}]},{question:"AgilePM says that [?] is sacrosanct and therefore cannot be adjusted",answers:[{text:"Time",correct:!0},{text:"The signed off Requirements spec",correct:!1},{text:"Timebox content",correct:!1},{text:"The lifecycle",correct:!1}]},{question:"What does AgilePM state about creating very detailed plans for more than a few weeks into the future?",answers:[{text:"This is wasted time and effort and can create a false sense of security, since it does not reflect the true sense of uncertainty",correct:!0},{text:"This is acceptable because the next step can be predicted with 100% accuracy but beyond that, no estimates or plans can be produced",correct:!1},{text:"This is unnecessary and creating fewer plans is a way of a good way saving paper",correct:!1},{text:"the Project Manager wants to do this, that is acceptable but the PM should leave the Team to focus on development work, not planning activities",correct:!1}]},{question:"In AgilePM, team members...",answers:[{text:".. organise their own work",correct:!0},{text:"take directions",correct:!1},{text:"compete",correct:!1},{text:"can slow down once the Must Haves have been achieved",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which of these behaviours would introduce risk into an AgilePM project?",answers:[{text:"Having a fully detailed specification at the start",correct:!0},{text:"Having a dedicated Solution Development Team",correct:!1},{text:"Having a part-time Business Ambassador",correct:!1},{text:"Having to produce a Business Case",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which AgilePM product includes an Outline Business Case and an Outline Solution?",answers:[{text:"Feasibility Assessment",correct:!0},{text:"Terms of Reference",correct:!1},{text:"Business Foundations",correct:!1},{text:"Solution Foundations",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which AgilePM lifecycle phases are completed sequentially and set the ground rules for the",answers:[{text:"Feasibility and Foundation",correct:!0},{text:"Pre-Project and Foundations",correct:!1},{text:"Foundations and Exploration",correct:!1},{text:"Engineering and Exploration",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which of the following statements is true?",answers:[{text:"Models can be temporary, transient, throwaway or may be a prototype which forms part of the eventual solution",correct:!0},{text:"Object Oriented modelling is a mandated part of AgilePM",correct:!1},{text:"AgilePM encourages formal modelling techniques, preferably in an electronic format, so they can be properly controlled",correct:!1},{text:"Models are always temporary, and are superceded once the real work starts",correct:!1}]},{question:"The AgilePM ethos of on-time, on-budget delivery means that ...",answers:[{text:"some of what was originally envisaged for delivery during an Increment may have to be left out",correct:!0},{text:"an overtime budget should be agreed in the early stages",correct:!1},{text:"AgilePM should only be used on projects where quality is negotiable",correct:!1},{text:"the Agile PM should identify what additional Solution Developers may be available later in the project, if problems occur",correct:!1}]},{question:"Managing an AgilePM project is about",answers:[{text:"enabling constant change whilst continuously correcting the course of the project in order to maintain its aim on target",correct:!0},{text:"continuously correcting the course of the team in order to maintain its aim on target",correct:!1},{text:"keeping the team focused on the Project Plan whilst continuously correcting the course of the project in order to maintain its aim on target",correct:!1},{text:"trying to prevent drift from the specification",correct:!1}]},{question:"How does AgilePM reduce the risk of the business not knowing exactly what they want?",answers:[{text:"By using the high-level baseline created during Foundations and allowing the detail to emerge through Iterative Development",correct:!0},{text:"By using a combination of Facilitated Workshops and Modelling during Foundations in order to visualise, agree and sign off the full Requirements Specification",correct:!1},{text:"By building contingency into the estimates",correct:!1},{text:"By enforcing Timeboxing",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which of these statements is true?",answers:[{text:"MoSCoW prioritisation is really only meaningful in a specified timeframe",correct:!0},{text:"MoSCoW prioritisation is a way of getting more done in a shorter timeframe",correct:!1},{text:"MoSCoW prioritisation defines the sequence of work, with Ms being done first and Ws last",correct:!1},{text:"MoSCoW prioritisation ensures the technical needs of the project are addressed early in the project",correct:!1}]},{question:"AgilePM advocates",answers:[{text:".incremental delivery, in order to deliver real business benefit early",correct:!0},{text:"daily delivery, since this is the objective of going agile",correct:!1},{text:"delivery into production every timebox",correct:!1},{text:"..a single delivery, to reduce the overheads of deployment on the project budget",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which of these statements is true....?",answers:[{text:"Feasibility and Foundations set the ground rules for the iterative and incremental development of the solution that is to follow",correct:!0},{text:"Feasibility and Foundations are optional phases, used when the Project has some spare time at the start",correct:!1},{text:"Feasibility and Foundations are needed so that the Project Manager can get plans approved",correct:!1},{text:"Feasibility and Foundations are necessary to get the Requirements Specification signed off",correct:!1}]},{question:"What does AgilePM state about products?",answers:[{text:"Not all products are required for every project and the formality associated with each product will vary from project to project and from organisation to organisation",correct:!0},{text:"All products are required for every project, in order to ensure the correct process is being followed",correct:!1},{text:"Not all products are required for every project, and the Solution Development Team members  should agree at the start which ones will be omitted",correct:!1},{text:"Although creating the products is useful, the primary focus is to have everything in place by the end of the project",correct:!1}]},{question:"What is the correct definition of a Should Have?",answers:[{text:"A requirement that is painful to leave out, but the solution would still be viable",correct:!0},{text:"A requirement that is wanted or desirable but less important",correct:!1},{text:"A requirement that Should be with the customer as early as possible",correct:!1},{text:"The lowest priority requirement - one that will be the first to be dropped if a problem occurs",correct:!1}]},{question:"The most common purpose for measuring within projects is ..",answers:[{text:"to understand enough about progress to allow the outcome to be controlled",correct:!0},{text:"....to enable management to set performance targets",correct:!1},{text:"....to reward success and punish failure",correct:!1},{text:"....to be able to provide statistics to justify slippage",correct:!1}]},{question:"An AgilePM Project Manager should set the objectives for the teams but leave them to get on with it unless",answers:[{text:"the controls exceed any tolerances that may have been set by the project\u2019s governing body",correct:!0},{text:"the PM believes they are making the wrong decision",correct:!1},{text:"the PM can see a better way of doing things",correct:!1},{text:"Any of the controls (Time, Cost, Features, Quality) need adjusting",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which planning product do the Solution Development Team use to record what they will be working on in the next few weeks, together with their MoSCoW priorities?",answers:[{text:"The Timebox Plan",correct:!0},{text:"The Delivery Plan",correct:!1},{text:"The Deployment Plan",correct:!1},{text:"The Development Approach",correct:!1}]},{question:"What product does AgilePM use to hold the work to be developed by the Solution Development Team?",answers:[{text:"Prioritised Requirements List",correct:!0},{text:"Product Backlog",correct:!1},{text:"Requirements Specification",correct:!1},{text:"To-do list",correct:!1}]},{question:"What does AgilePM state about Iterative Development?",answers:[{text:"terative Development needs to be controlled",correct:!0},{text:"Iterative Development needs to be constant",correct:!1},{text:"Iterative Development needs to be fun",correct:!1},{text:"Iterative Development needs to be quick",correct:!1}]},{question:"AgilePM..",answers:[{text:"encourages informal face-to-face communication at all levels",correct:!0},{text:"avoids formal documentation",correct:!1},{text:"..encourages informal face-to-face communication at all levels",correct:!1},{text:"replaces formal documentation with digital photographs",correct:!1}]},{question:"AgilePM's use of well defined timeboxes",answers:[{text:"assist the Project Manager and the Team to 'Demonstrate Control",correct:!0},{text:"ensures the Project Manager is kept away from the Development Team",correct:!1},{text:"..provides detailed information for the Project Manager to put into Microsoft Project",correct:!1},{text:".. keeps senior management happy and allows the team to get on with doing real work",correct:!1}]},{question:"If all requirements are defined as Must Haves...",answers:[{text:"the flexibility derived from the MoSCoW prioritisation would no longer work",correct:!0},{text:"the business get the full solution in a shorter timescale",correct:!1},{text:"then the priorities will need to be re-negotiated at a later date",correct:!1},{text:"AgilePM still works well, but the risks are slightly higher than usual",correct:!1}]},{question:"During the Investigation iteration of a Solution Development Timebox, why is it necessary to understand the full detail of all the work intended for completion in the Timebox?",answers:[{text:"To allow informed decisions later in the Timebox about what lower priority requirements maybe dropped if necessary",correct:!0},{text:"To allow the Agile PM to complete a properly detailed project plan",correct:!1},{text:"To allow the Business Ambassador to be confident the Team will be working hard",correct:!1},{text:"To highlight what work is highly unlikely to get done in the Timebox",correct:!1}]},{question:"In AgilePM, the quality of the solution is judged on",answers:[{text:"Whether it contains at least the Minimum Usable Subset",correct:!0},{text:"Whether it contains the Shoulds and Coulds",correct:!1},{text:"Whether it contains at least all the Musts and Shoulds",correct:!1},{text:"Whether all the requirements have been delivered",correct:!1}]},{question:"At which point in the Development Timebox are the Timebox objectives reviewed to gain a common understanding of what is to be achieved?",answers:[{text:"Timebox Kick-off",correct:!0},{text:"Investigation",correct:!1},{text:"Consolidation",correct:!1},{text:"Refinement",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which planning product do the Solution Development Team use to record what they will be working on in the next few weeks, together with their MoSCoW priorities?",answers:[{text:"The Timebox Plan",correct:!0},{text:"The Delivery Plan",correct:!1},{text:"The Deployment Plan",correct:!1},{text:"The Development Approach",correct:!1}]},{question:"What does AgilePM state as a benefit of Facilitated Workshops?",answers:[{text:"Building consensus",correct:!0},{text:"Building co-location",correct:!1},{text:"Building solutions",correct:!1},{text:"Building flow charts",correct:!1}]},{question:"'The skill and [?] of the Workshop Facilitator is important to ensure successful workshops'",answers:[{text:"independence",correct:!0},{text:"personality",correct:!1},{text:"versatility",correct:!1},{text:"power",correct:!1}]},{question:"The Daily Stand Up provides the primary mechanism for ...",answers:[{text:"the Team Leader to track progress and exert the necessary control over the work of the team to ensure on-time delivery",correct:!0},{text:"a team get-together during coffee break",correct:!1},{text:"...the Solution Developers to demonstrate the Evolving Solution",correct:!1},{text:"...the Solution Developers to apportion blame when things are not going well",correct:!1}]},{question:"In Timeboxing, significant change (for example, addition of additional requirements that cannot be traced back to the baseline created in Foundations ).",answers:[{text:"should be considered to be a change of scope and may require a more formal change control process",correct:!0},{text:"..should be encouraged as this is what teams expect",correct:!1},{text:"..should be tolerated and accommodated in existing plans and deadlines",correct:!1},{text:"should be refused under all circumstances",correct:!1}]},{question:"When creating a schedule of Timeboxes, the primary driver should always be",answers:[{text:"the business priority",correct:!0},{text:"the technical preferences",correct:!1},{text:"The Outline Plan",correct:!1},{text:"the view of the Project Manager",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which of these statements is true for AgilePM?",answers:[{text:"Increments are divided into Development Timeboxes",correct:!0},{text:"Development Timeboxes are subdivided into Increments",correct:!1},{text:"Increments are divided into Iterations",correct:!1},{text:"Each Development Timebox is immediately followed by an Increment",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which of these statements is true?",answers:[{text:"Scalability is a key attribute of AgilePM.",correct:!0},{text:"Scalability is a problem for AgilePM",correct:!1},{text:"AgilePM fits all shapes and sizes of project without any need for tailoring",correct:!1},{text:"AgilePM should not be used except on small projects",correct:!1}]},{question:"An AgilePM project should be able to demonstrate ...",answers:[{text:"predictability and control in a rapidly changing agile environment",correct:!0},{text:"predictability through controlling change",correct:!1},{text:"agility through removal of constraints",correct:!1},{text:"flexibility. Anything that delivers the end goal is acceptable",correct:!1}]},{question:"AgilePM expects early estimates",answers:[{text:"to give a broad picture, sufficient only to support the decision on whether or not to proceed",correct:!0},{text:"to lay down a precise shape for the project",correct:!1},{text:"to contain actual results and measures of velocity",correct:!1},{text:"to use function point analysis",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which of these statements is true for AgilePM?",answers:[{text:"Re-estimation happens throughout the project. Use MoSCoW prioritisation to remain on track",correct:!0},{text:"Re-estimation happens until the end of Foundations, when the Delivery Plan is issued",correct:!1},{text:"Re-estimation should only be carried out during the early Development Timeboxes",correct:!1},{text:"Re-estimation happens throughout the project. Use Iterative Development to remain on track",correct:!1}]},{question:"It is important to capture information on how much time is spent on delivering the products in order to..",answers:[{text:"ease the task of further estimating",correct:!0},{text:"identify the more productive members of the team",correct:!1},{text:"identify team members who are not as good as they should be",correct:!1},{text:"publish results of different teams in a league table",correct:!1}]},{question:"Within the Deployment phase there are three sub-phases or sections, what are they?",answers:[{text:"Assemble, review, deploy",correct:!0},{text:"Feasibility review, iterative development, release planning",correct:!1},{text:"Daily stand-ups, collaboration, deployment",correct:!1},{text:"Evolutionary development, foundations, pre-project",correct:!1}]},{question:"What role is responsible for the business case and project budget?",answers:[{text:"Business Sponsor",correct:!0},{text:"Business Visionary",correct:!1},{text:"Project Manager",correct:!1},{text:"Business Analysis",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which of the following is a benefit of using DSDM?",answers:[{text:"The risk of building the wrong solution is substantially reduced",correct:!0},{text:"A decreased reliance on customer collaboration",correct:!1},{text:"Less iterations needed to complete your project",correct:!1},{text:"The staff required to build a solution is substantially reduced",correct:!1}]},{question:"What does the 'S' in MoSCoW stand for?",answers:[{text:"Should have",correct:!0},{text:"Should not have",correct:!1},{text:"Standardization",correct:!1},{text:"Support Team",correct:!1}]},{question:"What does the 'S' in MoSCoW stand for?",answers:[{text:"Should have",correct:!0},{text:"Should not have",correct:!1},{text:"Standardization",correct:!1},{text:"Support Team",correct:!1}]},{question:"What are the two styles of timeboxes that DSDM recognizes?",answers:[{text:"Structured and free format",correct:!0},{text:"Daily stand-up and structured",correct:!1},{text:"Investigation and Refinement",correct:!1},{text:"Kick-off and Daily stand-up",correct:!1}]},{question:"The foundations phase occurs after the feasibility phase.",answers:[{text:"Correct",correct:!0},{text:"Incorrect",correct:!1},{text:"Half correct",correct:!1},{text:"Quarter correct",correct:!1}]},{question:"What is the purpose of a DSDM Coach?",answers:[{text:"They are responsible for helping the team understand the DSDM approach and help those outside of the team understand the process.",correct:!0},{text:"They are responsible for motivating the team to complete each evolutionary iteration",correct:!1},{text:"They manage the workshop process and are responsible for organizing workshop meetings",correct:!1},{text:'They are tasked with providing "Agile-style leadership"',correct:!1}]},{question:"During the foundations phase, you go through your iterative development process.",answers:[{text:"Incorrect",correct:!0},{text:"Correct",correct:!1},{text:"Half correct",correct:!1},{text:"Quarter correct",correct:!1}]},{question:"If you are nearing a deadline, compromising quality is an acceptable trade-off in DSDM",answers:[{text:"Incorrect",correct:!0},{text:"Correct",correct:!1},{text:"Half correct",correct:!1},{text:"Quarter correct",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which roles are part of the Project Level in DSDM?",answers:[{text:"Business Sponsor, Business Visionary, Technical Coordinator",correct:!0},{text:"Business Analyst, Project Manager, Business Ambassador",correct:!1},{text:"Technical Coordinator, Technical Adviser, Team Leader",correct:!1},{text:"Business Sponsor, DSDM Coach, Team Leader",correct:!1}]},{question:"What is Agile-Style leadership?",answers:[{text:"A servant-leader, not an authoritarian leader",correct:!0},{text:"An authoritarian leader, not a servant-leader",correct:!1},{text:"A team leader on the Solution Development Team (SDT)",correct:!1},{text:"Another name for a project manager of an Agile team",correct:!1}]},{question:"What does the 'W' stand for in MoSCoW?",answers:[{text:"Won't have this time",correct:!0},{text:"Would like to have this time",correct:!1},{text:"Want to have this time",correct:!1},{text:"Wish to have this time",correct:!1}]},{question:"A structured timebox contains three steps:",answers:[{text:"Investigation, refinement, consolidation\n",correct:!0},{text:"Investigation, review, collaboration",correct:!1},{text:"Free format, review, consolidation",correct:!1},{text:"Kick-off, refinement, collaboration",correct:!1}]},{question:"Who is responsible for leading a self-empowered team using facilitation rather than an authoritarian approach to leadership?",answers:[{text:"Project Manager",correct:!0},{text:"Team Leader",correct:!1},{text:"Business Sponsor",correct:!1},{text:"DSDM Coach",correct:!1}]},{question:"Fill in the blank. The __________ represents the business needs to the solution development team.",answers:[{text:"Business Ambassador",correct:!0},{text:"Business Analyst",correct:!1},{text:"Business Visionary",correct:!1},{text:"Project Manager",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which is NOT one of the 8 Principles of DSDM?",answers:[{text:"Individuals and interactions over processes and tool",correct:!0},{text:"Focus on the business need",correct:!1},{text:"Never compromise quality",correct:!1},{text:"Communicate continuously and clearly",correct:!1}]},{question:"What does the acronym SDT stand for?",answers:[{text:"Solution Development Team",correct:!0},{text:"Software Development Team",correct:!1},{text:"Standard DSDM Testing",correct:!1},{text:"Structured Development Timebox",correct:!1}]},{question:"For DSDM, the timebox duration of the daily stand-up should be:",answers:[{text:"2 minutes per person + 2 minutes",correct:!0},{text:"15 minutes",correct:!1},{text:"3 minutes per person + 3 minutes",correct:!1},{text:"20 minutes",correct:!1}]},{question:"'Must Have' items provide the Minimum Usable SubseT (MUST) of requirements which a project guarantees to deliver.",answers:[{text:"Correct",correct:!0},{text:"Incorrect",correct:!1},{text:"Half correct",correct:!1},{text:"Quarter correct",correct:!1}]},{question:"Fill in the blank. The __________ is an evolutionary product that provides a high-level definition of tools, techniques, customs, practices, and standards that will apply to the evolutionary development of the solution.",answers:[{text:"Development Approach Definition",correct:!0},{text:"Solution Architecture Definition",correct:!1},{text:"Delivery Plan",correct:!1},{text:"Management Approach Definition",correct:!1}]},{question:"In a structured timebox, the investigation phase should consume more than 10-20% of effort",answers:[{text:"Correct",correct:!0},{text:"Incorrect",correct:!1},{text:"Half correct",correct:!1},{text:"Quarter correct",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which role should ideally be filled by someone elected by their peers?",answers:[{text:"Team Leader",correct:!0},{text:"Project Manager",correct:!1},{text:"Business Ambassador",correct:!1},{text:"DSDM Coach",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which phase of the DSDM lifecycle do you do just enough work to determine if further planning is acceptable to the organization's goals?",answers:[{text:"Feasibility",correct:!0},{text:"Pre-project",correct:!1},{text:"Foundations",correct:!1},{text:"Deployment",correct:!1}]},{question:"An effective and successful team requires four elements. What are they?",answers:[{text:"Empowerment, stability, skills, size",correct:!0},{text:"Investigation, refinement, consolidation, close-out",correct:!1},{text:"Active, stable, committed, resourceful\n",correct:!1},{text:"Iterative development, continuously improving, empowered, skills",correct:!1}]},{question:"Fill in the blank. 'Could Have' items should typically only make up about ______ of total effort in a given iteration.",answers:[{text:"20%",correct:!0},{text:"60%",correct:!1},{text:"10 hours",correct:!1},{text:"10%",correct:!1}]},{question:"What is the Solution Architecture Definition?",answers:[{text:"An evolutionary product that covers both business and technical aspects of the solution",correct:!0},{text:"An evolutionary product that is designed for the solution development team laying out the definition of tools, techniques, and standards they will utilize in development of the solution",correct:!1},{text:"A feasibility product that provides a snapshot of the evolving solution",correct:!1},{text:"An evolutionary product that lays how the solution development team will deliver the final solution",correct:!1}]},{question:"hat are the two distinct type of products defined in DSDM?",answers:[{text:"Evolutionary products and milestone products",correct:!0},{text:"Roles and responsibilities",correct:!1},{text:"Terms of reference and the solution design",correct:!1},{text:"Documentation and the solution",correct:!1}]},{question:"When should the first instance of a solution be fully tested and potentially ready for deployment?",answers:[{text:"At the review stage of deployment",correct:!0},{text:"At the assemble stage of deployment",correct:!1},{text:"During the development iteration during that instance of the solution",correct:!1},{text:"At the evolutionary development stage",correct:!1}]},{question:"What does NOT occur in the Foundations phase of the DSDM lifecycle?",answers:[{text:"The first or foundational instance of development",correct:!0},{text:"Developing a strategy for deployment",correct:!1},{text:"Being able to commit to the delivery date of the first increment",correct:!1},{text:"A rough schedule of how many iterations needed and the duration of the iterations",correct:!1}]},{question:"The business analyst is not part of the solution development team",answers:[{text:"Incorrect",correct:!0},{text:"Correct",correct:!1},{text:"Half correct",correct:!1},{text:"Quarter correct",correct:!1}]},{question:"In a structured timebox, which step encompasses the bulk of the development, requirements work and testing of the timebox products?",answers:[{text:"Refinement",correct:!0},{text:"Investigation",correct:!1},{text:"Consolidation",correct:!1},{text:"Review",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which of the below is NOT a valid reason to assign a work item to a 'Must Have' status using MoSCoW prioritization?",answers:[{text:"It is important, but not critical",correct:!0},{text:"Not legal to leave it out",correct:!1},{text:"Product is unsafe without it",correct:!1},{text:"Solution will not function if it does not contain it",correct:!1}]},{question:"The Solution Developer is tasked with making sure the solution works",answers:[{text:"Incorrect",correct:!0},{text:"Correct",correct:!1},{text:"Half correct",correct:!1},{text:"Quarter correct",correct:!1}]},{question:"The business case is an evolutionary product that provides vision and justification for the project from the perspective of the business.",answers:[{text:"Correct",correct:!0},{text:"Incorrect",correct:!1},{text:"Half Incorrect",correct:!1},{text:"Quarter Incorrect",correct:!1}]},{question:"What is the Prioritized Requirements List (PRL)?",answers:[{text:"It is a high-level definition of the requirements that will be addressed by the project",correct:!0},{text:"It is an extremely detailed definition of the requirements that will be addressed by the project",correct:!1},{text:"It is a high-level design of the framework for the overall solution",correct:!1},{text:"It provides the definition of tools, techniques, customs, practices, and standards that will be applied to the development of the solution",correct:!1}]},{question:"What is the point of a timebox kick-off?",answers:[{text:"Review timebox objectives and gain a common understanding of the expected achievements",correct:!0},{text:"Provide a firm foundation for the work to be carried out by further clarifying requirements",correct:!1},{text:"Work to complete the planned development activities for the timebox",correct:!1},{text:"Gain formal acceptance of the products delivered from the timebox",correct:!1}]},{question:"What is the duration of a close-out for a structured timebox",answers:[{text:"Approximately 1-3 hours for a 2-3 week timebox",correct:!0},{text:"4 hours",correct:!1},{text:"8 hours for a month long sprint",correct:!1},{text:"Approximately 10-20% of the timebox",correct:!1}]},{question:"The Technical Coordinator is responsible for promoting appropriate standards of technical best practices.",answers:[{text:"Correct",correct:!0},{text:"Incorrect",correct:!1},{text:"Half incorrect",correct:!1},{text:"Quarter incorrect",correct:!1}]},{question:"The Business Analyst is responsible for encouraging full participation of team members within their defined roles.",answers:[{text:"Incorrect",correct:!0},{text:"Correct",correct:!1},{text:"Half correct",correct:!1},{text:"Quarter correct",correct:!1}]},{question:"Involving the right people at the right time falls under which of the 8 principles?",answers:[{text:"Collaborate",correct:!0},{text:"Build Incrementally from Firm Foundations",correct:!1},{text:"Communicate Continuously and Clearly",correct:!1},{text:"Focus on the Business Need",correct:!1}]}],v=function(e){Object(h.a)(o,e);var t=Object(u.a)(o);function o(e){var r;return Object(s.a)(this,o),(r=t.call(this,e)).state={displayedAnswer:r.filterQuestions("")},r.onFilterChange=r.onFilterChange.bind(Object(l.a)(r)),r}return Object(c.a)(o,[{key:"filterQuestions",value:function(e){var t=this,o=[];return w.forEach((function(r){(""===e||r.question.toLowerCase().includes(e.toLowerCase())||t.answerIncludeKeyword(r.answers,e))&&o.push(i.a.createElement(m.a,{item:!0,xs:12,sm:6},i.a.createElement(x.a,{style:{animation:b.animations.popIn,backgroundColor:"rgba(253, 247, 237, 0.4)",maxWidth:"95%",margin:"0 auto",height:"auto"}},i.a.createElement(f.a,null,i.a.createElement(g.a,{color:"textPrimary",gutterBottom:!0},i.a.createElement("b",null,r.question)),i.a.createElement("p",{style:{lineHeight:"1.5"}},i.a.createElement("span",{role:"img","aria-label":"correct"},"\u2705")," ",i.a.createElement("span",null,r.answers[0].text),i.a.createElement("br",null),i.a.createElement("br",null),i.a.createElement("span",{role:"img","aria-label":"incorrect"},"\u274c")," ",i.a.createElement("span",null,r.answers[1].text),i.a.createElement("br",null),i.a.createElement("br",null),i.a.createElement("span",{role:"img","aria-label":"incorrect"},"\u274c")," ",i.a.createElement("span",null,r.answers[2].text),i.a.createElement("br",null),i.a.createElement("br",null),i.a.createElement("span",{role:"img","aria-label":"incorrect"},"\u274c")," ",i.a.createElement("span",null,r.answers[3].text),i.a.createElement("br",null))))))})),o}},{key:"answerIncludeKeyword",value:function(e,t){for(var o=0;o<e.length;o++)if(e[o].text.toLowerCase().includes(t.toLowerCase()))return!0;return!1}},{key:"onFilterChange",value:function(e){this.setState({displayedAnswer:this.filterQuestions(e.currentTarget.value)})}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this.props.classes;return i.a.createElement("div",{className:e.root},i.a.createElement(m.a,{container:!0,className:e.container,spacing:3},i.a.createElement(m.a,{item:!0,xs:12},i.a.createElement(p.a,{id:"filled-basic",label:"Keyword",variant:"outlined",onChange:this.onFilterChange,fullWidth:!0})),this.state.displayedAnswer))}}]),o}(i.a.Component),y=Object(d.a)((function(e){return{root:{height:"100%",width:"100%",position:"absolute",top:"0",left:"0"},container:{width:"95%",maxWidth:"800px",margin:"0 auto",marginTop:"100px"}}}))(v);o(45),Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));a.a.render(i.a.createElement(i.a.StrictMode,null,i.a.createElement("link",{rel:"stylesheet",href:"https://fonts.googleapis.com/icon?family=Material+Icons"}),i.a.createElement(y,null)),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(e){e.unregister()})).catch((function(e){console.error(e.message)}))}},[[36,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.d17a7cd1.chunk.js.map